http://www.radiantbarrier.com/privacy-policy/

We know that your privacy is very important to you. Innovative Insulation is deeply committed to your right to privacy and takes your privacy seriously. Our goal is to treat any personal information you provide us with the utmost respect and in strict confidence.
Because we gather certain types of information about the users of the network of sites and services of Innovative Insulation (“Innovative Insulation”), we believe you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
Information Collection and Use
Innovative Insulation is the sole owner of the personal information collected on this web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Innovative Insulation collects information from our users for the sole purpose of communicating with you about orders you have placed or questions you have asked. Innovative Insulation may ask for your contact information (such as your e-mail address, physical address, or phone number). Innovative Insulation may also ask for such information at other times, such when you request information or when you decide to purchase products from us. Innovative Insulation will not disclose any of your personal information, except as described in this Privacy Policy, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Innovative Insulation.
Third-Party Information Collection
We also use third-party services, such as Google Analytics, to track traffic statistics to our site. Their purpose is so that we can improve our web site and products.
We have implemented and use Display Advertising as well as Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites across the Internet. We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on visits to our website.
You may opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising using the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information associated with the user’s visit to the site. Cookies cannot tell us who you are or give us any personally identifiable information about you, nor can they be used to access information on your computer.
Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s Ads Preference Manager. Alternatively, you can opt out of many other third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Links
This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Innovative Insulation is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Notification of Changes; Conflicts
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will user information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. This page reflects the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy, and thus takes precedence over information provided in other documents.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (800) 825-0123 or via email.
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Saint Martin (French part)
Sint Maarten (Dutch part)
Virgin Islands, U.S.
